Privacy Policy
==============

Please review the following terms carefully. If you do not agree with the Privacy Policy, then you do not have the right to view, access, purchase any product from or otherwise use this Website and, accordingly, you should not do so. Your continued use of this Website constitutes your acceptance of our Privacy Policy.

Information We Collect
======================

Information Provided by You: The type of Personal Information that we may collect depends on your use of this Website and what information you provide to us. We may collect Personal Information that you provide to us when you place an order through our website or customer service agents, or if you create or update an account on our website. “Personal Information” is information that can be used to identify you individually, and includes items such as your name, home address, e-mail address, telephone number, demographic information, and/or payment card information, if used to make a purchase from our Website. If you maintain an account on our website, Personal Information may also include a user name, password and answers to our security questions.

Cookies and Other Technology: Like many sites, our Website employs cookies, JavaScript tags, pixels and Web beacons (also known as clear GIF technology or "action tags") to speed your navigation of our Website, recognize you and your access privileges, and track usage of our Website. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive. We use both persistent cookies and third-party cookies. Persistent and third-party cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our customers to enhance your experience on our Website. Persistent cookies are used to make it easier for you to navigate our Website, and remain on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Third party cookies are only used for short-term tracking.

Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can remove cookies by following the directions provided in your Internet browser's "Help" file. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Website, but your ability to use some areas of our Website, such as a shopping cart, may be limited and may not function properly.

Analytical Information: We and our third-party service providers may also use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect information about how this Website is accessed and used (known as "Usage Information"). “Usage Information” may include the type of browser and device you used to access our Website, your operating system and application version, the web pages accessed by you, the time you accessed these web pages, preceding web page views, and your use of any features or applications on this Website. Statistical data like this helps us understand what is interesting and relevant to our customers, so we can best adapt our content for our customers’ benefit.

We and our third-party service providers may also automatically collect an IP address or other unique identifier information from the computer, mobile device, technology or other device you use to access this Website. We may use this information to, amongst other things, administer this Website, help diagnose server problems, analyze trends, track web page movements, help identify you and your shopping cart, and gather broad demographic information for collected use.

Third Party Information
=======================

We also may receive information about you from third parties that include our products or promotional offers if you opt-in to receive information from us. You may also choose to participate in a third-party app or social media site through which you allow us to collect information about you, including Personal Information.

Use and Sharing of Information
==============================

We use the information that we collect about you for a variety reasons, including the following:

* Verifying your identity;
* Fulfilling your product orders;
* Responding to your questions;
* Providing you with access to certain areas and features of this Website;
* Communicating with you about your purchases and activities on this Website;
* Offers regarding products and services we may provide to you directly or through third-party partners (unless you opt-out of such communications);
* Improving the Website and our customers’ experience; and
* Sending notices or information.

If you provide us with a payment card when placing an order on our website, we use third-parties to validate your card, authenticate your identity and “tokenize” your payment credentials to make your payments more secure. Your “tokenized” credentials will be stored in your account in order to help make future purchases more convenient. You may delete or edit the stored payment methods in your account at any time by visiting our website or contacting customer support.

We may share your Personal Information with our parent entities, subsidiaries and affiliates. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not share any of your Personal Information with third parties without your specific consent. We may share non-personal information, such as user statistics or demographics, as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We also contract with certain vendors to assist us in providing services to our customers. These vendors use the Personal Information that you submit to us in order to perform the following tasks:

• Order processing at checkout;

• Credit card authorization, tokenization and identity verification;

• Order shipping and handling;

• Emailing newsletters and other promotional materials;

• Improving our Website and related content and features;

• Storing and “backing up” our customer records.

Finally, notwithstanding the foregoing, we may transfer and disclose information, including your Personal Information, Usage Information, and Identifying Information, including IP address, to third parties to comply with a legal obligation; at the request of governmental authorities; or otherwise to protect the rights, property, safety, or security of third parties, users of this Website, or the public.

Consent to Processing Information
=================================

This Website is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the State of California and the United States, and is intended for the enjoyment of residents of the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States.

By using this Website, or providing us with any information, you (a) acknowledge that this Website is subject to the laws of the State of California and the United States, (b) consent to the collection, processing, maintenance and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other applicable territories, in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive or equivalent to those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen, and (c) waive any claims that may arise under those laws.

Security and Your Information
=============================

No data transmission over the Internet or website can be guaranteed to be secure from intrusion. However, we maintain commercially reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your Personal Information in accordance with data protection legislative requirements. We follow the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI DSS) when handling credit card data. We also recommend that you take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your account through shared or public computers, devices, and applications.

Our Children’s Policy
=====================

This Website is not directed to children under the age of thirteen (13). Children may not use our services, and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13). We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who address our Website. If a child has provided us with personal information, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities.

For California Residents
========================

Many browsers have a “Do Not Track” feature that allows you to instruct websites that you do not want them to track your online activities. These browser features are not uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to this feature.

California residents who have provided their personal information to us may request data regarding disclosures of their information to third parties for direct marketing purposes.

Changes and Updates to our Privacy Policy
=========================================

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice to you. Any changes that we make will be effective immediately upon our posting of the revised Privacy Policy on this Website. Your continued use of this Website constitutes your consent to any changes made. We will use your Personal Information in a manner consistent with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time you submitted your Personal Information, unless you later consent to a revised policy. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

How to Opt-Out of Target Advertising
====================================

If you do not wish to receive targeted advertising, you have the option to opt-out. You can opt-out by visiting the "Manage Subscriptions" tab at the bottom of any emailed advertisement. Opt- out requests will be processed within ten (10) business days. Please note that even if you remove your information (i.e., opt-out), you will still see our advertisements while browsing this Website or the Internet.
